<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="fill_parent"
  xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    <include layout="@layout/acti_title_view" />
    <TextView android:id="@id/tv_protocol" android:padding="5.0dip" android:visibility="gone" android:scrollbars="vertical" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_marginTop="5.0dip" android:text="\u0009\u0009\u0009《用户注册协议》是制约用户滥用违法的手段干扰网站的运行的手段。\n 　　 用户名和昵称的注册与使用应符合网络道德，遵守中华人民共和国的相关法律法规。\n 　　 用户名和昵称中不能含有威胁、淫秽、漫骂、非法、侵害他人权益等有争议性的文字。\n 　　 注册成功后，会员必须保护好自己的帐号和密码，因会员本人泄露而造成的任何损失由会员本人负责。\n 　　 不得盗用他人帐号，由此行为造成的后果自负。\n 　　您的个人信息将在下述情况下部分或全部被披露：\n 　　 经您同意，向第三方披露；\n 　　 如您是合资格的知识产权投诉人并已提起投诉，应被投诉人要求，向被投诉人披露，以便双方处理可能的权利纠纷；\n 　　 根据法律的有关规定，或者行政或司法机构的要求，向第三方或者行政、司法机构披露；\n 　　 如果您出现违反中国有关法律或者网站政策的情况，需要向第三方披露；\n 　　 为提供你所要求的产品和服务，而必须和第三方分享您的个人信息；\n 　　 其他本网站根据法律或者网站政策认为合适的披露\n 　　一、责任说明\n 　　基于技术和不可预见的原因而导致的服务中断，或者因会员的非法操作而造成的损失，“法律百科”不负责任。会员应当自行承担一切因自身行为而直接或者间接导致的民事或刑事法律责任。\n 　　二、会员必须做到：\n 　　1、不得利用本站危害国家安全、泄露国家秘密，不得侵犯国家社会集体的和公民的合法权益，不得利用本站制作、复制和传播下列信息：\n 　　（1）煽动抗拒、破坏宪法和法律、行政法规实施的；\n 　　（2）煽动颠覆国家政权，推翻社会主义制度的；\n 　　（3）煽动分裂国家、破坏国家统一的；\n 　　（4）煽动民族仇恨、民族歧视，破坏民族团结的；\n 　　（5）捏造或者歪曲事实，散布谣言，扰乱社会秩序的；\n 　　（6）宣扬封建迷信、淫秽、色情、赌博、暴力、凶杀、恐怖、教唆犯罪的；\n 　　（7）公然侮辱他人或者捏造事实诽谤他人的，或者进行其他恶意攻击的；\n 　　（8）损害国家机关信誉的；\n 　　（9）其他违反宪法和法律行政法规的；\n 　　（10）进行商业广告行为的。" />
    <TextView android:id="@id/tv_protocol_en" android:padding="5.0dip" android:visibility="gone" android:scrollbars="vertical" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_marginTop="5.0dip" android:text="\u0009\u0009\u0009《User registration protocol》 is a means to restrict users from abusing illegal means. \n The user name and nickname registration and use in accordance with the network ethics, abide by the relevant laws and regulations of the people's Republic of china. \n No - user ID and nickname containing obscene, abusive, threatening, illegal infringement of the rights of others, such controversial words. \n  after successful registration, the member must protect your username and password, any loss caused by the member himself leaked by the member himself responsible for. \n No - theft account, which caused by the behavior of the consequences. \n Your personal information will be disclosed in the following circumstances: \n - with your consent, disclosed to third parties; \n  if you are eligible people complained of intellectual property rights and has filed a complaint, should be complainant demands to the respondent disclosure to both sides to deal with possible right dispute; n  according to the relevant provisions of the law, or administrative or judicial body of the request, or to the third party of administrative and judicial institutions to disclose. n If you violate the Chinese laws or policies of the site, need to be disclosed to third parties; \n - provide you the required products and services, and third parties must share your personal information; \n The rest of this web site by law or policy that appropriate disclosure of \n One, the responsibility of \n Based on the technical and unforeseen causes of service disruption, or due to the loss of the illegal operation of the member, the legal encyclopedia is not responsible. Members shall bear all the civil or criminal liability, which is directly or indirectly caused by their own actions. \n Two, members must be: \n 1, shall not use this site to endanger national security, disclose state secrets, and shall not infringe upon the legitimate rights and interests of the national community and citizens, shall not use this site to produce, copy and disseminate the following information: \n (1) to resist or damage to the Constitution and laws and regulations of the law and administrative regulations; \n (2) to overthrow the state power and to overthrow the socialist system; \n (3) the state of the nation and the destruction of the state of the nation; \n (4) incitement to ethnic hatred, ethnic discrimination, and undermine national unity; \n (5) fabricating or distorting the facts, spreading rumors, disrupting social order; \n (6) promoting the feudal superstition, pornography, gambling, violence, murder, terror, and the crime of solicitation; \n (7) the fact that a person is an insult to another, or that a person is, or is made up of facts, or slander others, or other malicious attacks, \n (8) damage to the credibility of the state organs; \n (9) other violations of the Constitution and laws and regulations; \n (10) the conduct of commercial advertising." />
</LinearLayout>